Guide to the Cornell University Library Office of the Assistant Director for the Development of Collections records
Cornell University Library Office of the Assistant Director for the Development of Collections records.
- Reichmann, Felix. "Purchase of Out-of-Print Material in American University Libraries." Library Trends, Jan. 1970 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Questionnaire, Correpondence, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Questionnaires: Extra, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Questionnaires on the Acquisitions of Out of Print Material (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Questionnaires: Used, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Replies, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Standard Forms for Qustionnaires - Letter of Instruction, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Standard Thank-You Forms for Questionnaire Replies, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Companhia Johnson (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Hull, Col. Frank Library, 1949-1951 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Hull Library (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Hull Library: Index (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Subject Files, Incoming Correspondence and Outgoing Correspondence, 1961 (Box 13)
- Subject Files, Incoming Correspondence and Outgoing Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 14)
- Subject Files, Incoming Correspondence and Outgoing Correspondence, 1962 (Box 15)
- Subject Files, Incoming Correspondence and Outgoing Correspondence, 1965 (Box 16)
- Subject Files, Incoming Correspondence and Outgoing Correspondence, 1966 (Box 17)
- Subject Files, Incoming Correspondence and Outgoing Correspondence, 1967 (Box 18)
- Subject Files, Incoming Correspondence and Outgoing Correspondence (also some pamphlets), 1967 (Box 19)
- Acquisitions - Africa, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - Americas, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - Asia, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - Australia, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - Canada, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - European, Austria to Denmark, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - European, England, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - European, France, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - European, Germany, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - European, Greece to Italy, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - European, Netherlands to Switzerland, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - Israel, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - Jamaca - West Indies, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - Russia, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - Allen, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - Harrassowitz, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - Nardecchia, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - Nijhoff, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - United States, A-B, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - United States, C, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - United States, D-G, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - United States, H, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - United States, I-L, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - United States, M, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - United States, N-Q, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - United States, R, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - United States, S, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - United States, T-Z, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - Kraus, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - H.P. Kraus, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - Library of Congress, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - A to Y (1 file for each letter - 25 files), 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Campus Store Committee, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Duplicate Sales, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Reclassification, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - PL-480, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Personnel, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Microfilm Orders, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Biological Sciences, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Archival Projects, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Budget, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Center for Research Libraries, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Conrell Univ., 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Monthly Report, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Echols, John, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Kaser, David, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Kaske, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Malott, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Perkins, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Psycology Dept., 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Calif., Univ. of Berkeley, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Research Club, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Reviews, Books and Articles, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Albany Survey, 1968 (Box 20)
- General - Library Associates, 1968 (Box 20)
- Acquisitions - Americas, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - Asia, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - Australia, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - European, Australia to Denmark, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - European, England, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - European, France, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - European, Germany, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - European, Lebanon, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - European, Greece to Italy, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - European, Liechtenstein, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - European, Netherlands to Switzerland, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - European, Israel, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - European, Russia, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - Allen, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - Harrassowitz, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - Nardecchia, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - Nijhoff, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - United States, A-B, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - United States, C, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - United States, D-G, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - United States, I-L, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - United States, M, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - United States, N-Q, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - United States, R, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - United States, S, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - United States, T-Z, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - Kraus, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - H.P. Kraus, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - Library of Congress, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - Microfilm Orders, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - Budget, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - Center for Research Libraries, 1969 (Box 21)
- Acquisitions - Kress Foundation, 1969 (Box 21)
- General - Monthly Report, 1969 (Box 21)
- General - Conrell Univ., General File, 1969 (Box 21)
- General - A to Z (26 files), 1969 (Box 21)
- General - Personnel, 1969 (Box 21)
- General - Reclassification, 1969 (Box 21)
- General - Research Club, 1969 (Box 21)
- General - Personal Correspondence, 1969 (Box 21)
- General - Acquisitions Policy, 1969 (Box 21)
- General Files - Kaser, David, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - Soviet Studies, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - Echols, John, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - SEA Dept., 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - Reviews, Bochum and Busse - Ernestus, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - Reviews, Klassifikations Systems und Thesauri, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - ALA, Annual Reports, 1967-1968; 1966-1967 (Box 22)
- General Files - ALA, Committee (general file), 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - ALA, Elizabeth Rodell, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - ALA, RTSD, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - ALA, Cataloguing: Classification Section, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - ALA, Bal Harbour, Fla./Midwinter Mtg., 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - ALA, Materials Price Index Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - ALA, Annual Reports from Committees, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - ALA, Acquisitions Section, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - ALA, Executive Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - ALA, Interdivisional Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - ALA, Committee Chairmen and Members - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - ALA, Kansas City Planning Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - ALA, Kansas City Conference, 1968 (Box 22)
- General Files - Microcard Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- General Files - New York Library Assoc. (NYLA), 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- Dr. Reichmann's Seminars, Courses, Articles, misc. - History of the Book, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- Dr. Reichmann's Seminars, Courses, Articles, misc. - Title page (Article), 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- Dr. Reichmann's Seminars, Courses, Articles, misc. - Bibliography on the Title Page, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- Dr. Reichmann's Seminars, Courses, Articles, misc. - Cornell Seminar on Hisory of the Book, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- Dr. Reichmann's Seminars, Courses, Articles, misc. - Students (Spring 1969 ) (Box 22)
- Dr. Reichmann's Seminars, Courses, Articles, misc. - Students (Fall 1968 ) (Box 22)
- Dr. Reichmann's Seminars, Courses, Articles, misc. - Students (Fall 1968, Syracuse) (Box 22)
- Dr. Reichmann's Seminars, Courses, Articles, misc. - Course Outline and Notes, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- Dr. Reichmann's Seminars, Courses, Articles, misc. - Preliminary Bibliography (Course), 1968-1969 (Box 22)
- Dr. Reichmann's Seminars, Courses, Articles, misc. - Bibliography (Seminar), 1968-1969 (Box 22)